{"ChineseSL":[],"PhysicsHL":[{"question":"Which of the followings is Physics HL topic?","optionA":"Atomic, nuclear, and particle physics","optionB":"Wave phenomena","optionC":"Circular motion and gravition","optionD":"Relativity","answer":1},{"question":"How long does Physics HL paper 1 take?","optionA":"30 min","optionB":"45 min","optionC":"1 h","optionD":"1.5 h","answer":2},{"question":"Do students need to pay more for HL Physics","optionA":"Yes, because it is an advanced study.","optionB":"Yes, because our campus need money.","optionC":"No, because students are poor.","optionD":"No, because students are consumers.","answer":3},{"question":"What is Mr. Constantinos' favorite pet phrase?","optionA":"Simple harmonic motion.","optionB":"It is more easy.","optionC":"Go out.","optionD":"Zero motivation.","answer":1},{"question":"Where is Physics office?","optionA":"B201","optionB":"B202","optionC":"B203","optionD":"B302","answer":2}],"PhysicsSL":[{"question":"Is Physics an optional course?","optionA":"Yes, because Physics is so important!","optionB":"No, because it is just one part of the Science.","optionC":"Yes, because IBO said so.","optionD":"No, because Mr.Constantinos' English is very poor.","answer":1},{"question":"Can different students choose different optional topics in Physics?","optionA":"Yes. FREEDOM!","optionB":"No. Teachers are almighty.","optionC":"Maybe. It depends on students.","optionD":"Maybe, it depends on luck.","answer":3},{"question":"How many non-optional SL topics are there in Physics course?","optionA":"6","optionB":"7","optionC":"8","optionD":"9","answer":2},{"question":"How many papers do students have to finish in the global exam?","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","answer":2},{"question":"Which paper is multiple-choice paper?","optionA":"Paper 1","optionB":"Paper 2","optionC":"Paper 3","optionD":"There is no multiple choice.","answer":0},{"question":"What additional equipments or materials you can have during paper 1?","optionA":"None","optionB":"Calculator","optionC":"Formula booklet","optionD":"Calculator and formula booklet","answer":2},{"question":"How long does it take to finish SL paper 2?","optionA":"1.25 h","optionB":"1.5 h","optionC":"1.75 h","optionD":"2 h","answer":0},{"question":"What is Mr. Constantinos' previous job?","optionA":"Vanstantinos","optionB":"Body-builder coach","optionC":"Wrestler","optionD":"Bomb disposal unit","answer":3},{"question":"What is the highest score you can get for IA?","optionA":"12","optionB":"24","optionC":"25","optionD":"30","answer":1},{"question":"What is your best revision material for SL Physics?","optionA":"End of chapter practices","optionB":"NFLS.IO past papers","optionC":"AP Physics past papers","optionD":"No need for revision","answer":2}],"VisualArtsSL":[{"question":"Which factor is the most important one in IB visual art?","optionA":"Concepts ( e.g symbols )","optionB":"Techniques ( e.g realism )","optionC":"Neither","optionD":"I don't know :)","answer":0},{"question":"Which form of work will be demonstrated mainly in IB visual art?","optionA":"Individual. I'm the chosen one.","optionB":"Team work. Together we're strong.","optionC":"Both","optionD":"Neither","answer":2},{"question":"What's the difference between SL arts and HL arts in the first year?","optionA":"SL students will have fewer projects to do.","optionB":"SL students will get an easy 7.","optionC":"SL arts is for students who only consider arts as a hobby.","optionD":"No difference.","answer":3},{"question":"How many A3 pages should we write down for one art project?","optionA":"10","optionB":"11","optionC":"12","optionD":"It depends on the quality.","answer":3},{"question":"How many art forms should a SL student use at least?","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","answer":1},{"question":"Can students pick two forms from one dimension? e.g sketching and painting","optionA":"Yes, because it's all about art.","optionB":"Yes, because they are different.","optionC":"No, because they are both about 2D.","optionD":"No, because they are the same.","answer":2},{"question":"What kind of project will be counted in the end of semester score?","optionA":"Art journal (paper)","optionB":"Process portfolio (digital)","optionC":"Exhibition projects and describtion","optionD":"All of above","answer":3},{"question":"Will art students have test?","optionA":"Yes, because tests are part of IB.","optionB":"Yes, because tests will judge our IB score.","optionC":"No, because tests are rubbish.","optionD":"No, because the teachers judge students through other ways.","answer":3},{"question":"Which part of the art journal will be the most valuable one?","optionA":"Inspiration","optionB":"Process","optionC":"Reflection","optionD":"Final product","answer":1},{"question":"How many art projects for exhibition will a SL student need to hang in?","optionA":"1~3","optionB":"2~5","optionC":"3~7","optionD":"4~9","answer":2}],"MathematicsHL":[{"question":"How many papers do students need to take in HL math?","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","answer":1},{"question":"Which of the following equipments or materials can students take during paper 1?","optionA":"Non-graphic calculator","optionB":"GDC","optionC":"Formula booklet","optionD":"Calculator and booklet","answer":2},{"question":"Why can't some students choose HL math?","optionA":"Because Principle Leigh does not like math.","optionB":"Because the their Maths scores for IGCSE are poor.","optionC":"Because they are stupid.","optionD":"Because IBO wants this limitation.","answer":1},{"question":"Can students play Kahoot! in HL math class?","optionA":"Yes, because it is funny.","optionB":"Yes, because it helps us review.","optionC":"No, because we have kahoot.nfls.io.","optionD":"No, because students shouldn't play games.","answer":1},{"question":"Can students choose topics in the textbook as IA topic for HL math?","optionA":"Yes, because it can help us review.","optionB":"No, because IB need be risk-takers.","optionC":"Yes, because those topics are difficult.","optionD":"No, because the syllabus requires us to go beyond textbook.","answer":3}],"VisualArtsHL":[]}